<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CLI on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CLI on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:37:54 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CLI : oc 설정</title>
      <link>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/cli1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:22:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/cli1/</guid>
      <description>okd github okd documentation oc download  Kubernetes의 명령줄 인터페이스(CLI) kubectl는 Kubernetes 클러스터에 대해 명령을 실행하는 데 사용됩니다. OKD는 Kubernetes 클러스터 위에서 실행되기 때문에 kubectl도 oc CLI에 포함됩니다.
1. oc download  oc download  OS에 맞게 실행파일을 다운로드한다.   OKD web-console에서 직접 다운로드  우측 상단의 about 링크를 눌러 Command line tools로 이동해 다운로드 받을 수 있다.      2. 압축 해제  적당한 경로에 압축을 해제한다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLI2 : Basic Commands</title>
      <link>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/cli2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:53:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/cli2/</guid>
      <description>No Command Description     1 new-project Request a new Project   2 new-app Request a new application   3 projects Display existing project   4 project Switch to another project    1. new-project C:\Users\user&amp;gt;oc new-project --help Create a new project for yourself. If your administrator allows self-service, this command will create a new project for you and assign you as the project admin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLI3 : oc apply</title>
      <link>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/cli3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 09:35:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluewhale-users.github.io/ko/okd/cli/cli3/</guid>
      <description>oc apply는 파일 또는 stdin을 통해 리소스 구성을 적용합니다.
&amp;gt;oc apply --help Apply a configuration to a resource by filename or stdin. The resource name must be specified. This resource will be created if it doesn&amp;#39;t exist yet. To use &amp;#39;apply&amp;#39;, always create the resource initially with either &amp;#39;apply&amp;#39; or &amp;#39;create --save-config&amp;#39;. JSON and YAML formats are accepted. Alpha Disclaimer: the --prune functionality is not yet complete. Do not use unless you are aware of what the current state is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
